Dang it! I'm not getting through!
まったく携帯が通じない
Jamming?
電波障害
"Maybe"?! "Maybe" doesn't cut it!
Identify the problem ASAP!
かもしれない
「かも」じゃ困るでしょ
早く原因を調べて
危ないです
Look out! The Little Lady is teed off.
お嬢が荒れてます
HQ is friggin' inept.
本部の手際が悪すぎなの
They tick me off...
イライラする連中だ
We're meeting up with Valmet and Tojo
in the next town and I can't reach them!
次の街で待ち合わせのバルメとトージョと連絡できない
Although this goes without saying...
それもさることながら
BRDM-2U：BRDM-2两栖装甲侦察车由苏联杰特科夫设计局设计，在BRDM-1装甲侦察车的基础上
改进而成。采用4×4驱动，战斗全重7吨，车长5.75米，宽2.35米，高2.31米。车底距地0.43米，
轮距1.84米，可越1.25米宽的嚎沟，最大爬坡度达31°。乘员4人，除车长和驾驶员外，
战斗室内有2名乘员，BRDM-2U是BRDM衍生型号，为战斗指挥车。
...who are those guys?
何なのあいつら
We have always stood on the borderland.
我们始终踱步于境界线之上
I'm enjoying the view from here.
皆因此境风景独好
Eeny,meeny,miny,moe...
一，二，三，四...
Eeny, meeny, miny, moe...
much the same
其实都一样
We have always stood on the borderland.
我们始终踱步于境界线之上
日听   yaya
I'm enjoying the view from here.
皆因此境风景独好
日听      奶昔
神
岛
&
诸
恶
魔
Pike or shield?
Pike or shield?  負けたくはない　でも傷つけたくもない
矛 or 盾？ 不想认输 可是又不愿受伤害
Maketaku wa nai demo kizu tsuketaku mo nai
时轴      两仪
Te ni totte tashikameteta
手に取って　確かめてた
先挑一样在手中仔细掂量
Kitto modorenain datte
きっと戻れないんだって
可是发现再要反悔为时已晚
Whose side are you on?
你选的是哪边？
翻译  TL旧民
(Don't want to know!) Omoide wa kase
Don't want to know!  思い出は枷
Don't want to know!  思念是枷锁
注释   TL旧民
(Don't want to know!) Atozuke no love
Don't want to know!  後付けのlove
Don't want to know!  追悔莫及的爱
后期  aoi
Don't want to know!  優しさは仇
Don't want to know!  温柔是弱点
(Don't want to know!) Yasashisa wa ada
We have always stood on the borderland.
我们始终踱步于境界线之上
压制   娜夏
Hirogeru ryoute keep balance
広げる両手　keep balance
张开双臂保持平衡
より高く飛べる方へ
向着更高的天空振臂而飞
Yori takaku toberu hou he
Mamoritai yo
守りたいよ 僕らの翼のないこの背中に背負った
唯独想保护的是.. 背负于我们那折翼的背膀之上的
Bokura no tsubasa no nai kono senaka ni seotta
Reality and Dream
Reality & Dream
真实 & 梦想
Reality and Dream
两仪
Reality & Dream
真实 & 梦想
Reality and Dream
Reality & Dream
真实 & 梦想
That vehicle belongs to the national border police.
この国の国境警備車両だ
What should we do, Koko?
どうする　ココ
There's no need to stop.
止まることないよ
If they think a mere LAV can
stop a 20-ton truck, I'd love--
軽WAVなんかで
WAV："wheeled armored vehicle"的缩写，中文名为轮式装甲车
20Tトラックが止めれるもんなら止めて
Colt M733 "Abu Dhabi Carbine":680（760）mm 重量2.4kg
口径5.56mm*45 发射形式S/3 制造国：美国
Glock 17 :全长186mm 重量625g 口径9mm*19 装弹数17/19/33+1 制造国：奥地利
Colt M4A1 Carbine：全长760（840）mm 重量2.68kg 口径5.56mm*45
装弹数20/30 连射速度850发/分 发射形式S/F 制造国：美国加拿大
Crap! It was a trap.
くそ　トラップか
Hey! Don't go outside, Little Lady!
おい　出んな　お嬢
Wh-What in the world?!
な
なんじゃこりゃ
へっへへ　パイプラインの奪い合いか
They're fighting over a pipeline.
This is currently a raging battlefield.
こりゃもう立派に戦闘地帯だぜ
It's why your phone wasn't gettin' through, Koko.
電話通じねえ理由はこれだな　ココ
GMS携帯電話基地とか
GMS mobile phone base stations,
telephone offices,
電話局とか
and microwave transmission sites
have been getting blown up by both sides.
マイクロ波通信の施設とかを　吹っ飛ばされたり　吹っ飛ばしたり
It's advantageous for them to control information.
したらそれを逆手に
情報統制するんだ
Even satellites aren't perfect. This is a covert war.
衛星だって万能じゃねえ
秘密裏の戦闘
Hmm... You sure know a lot about this, Lehm.
へえ　詳しいですね　レームさん
You think?
そうかね
There are two over-sized trucks
and a unit equipped with small arms.
二台の大型トラックと
小銃で武装の一個分隊
USSR AKS74U "Krinkov"：全长730（490）mm 重量3.2kg 口径5.45mm*39
装弹30 连射速800发/分 发射形式S/F 制造国：苏联
護衛要員に見える
They appear to be guards.
And there's an out-of-place woman throwing a fit.
あと　場違いな女が喚いてる
That's our dealer. Don't fire.
それはバイヤーだ　撃つな
Yeah, yeah. We aren't your enemies.
はいはい
敵じゃないよ
Not that we're your friends, either.
友達でもないけど
Well, I'm glad you made it, Miss Hekmatyar.
いやあ　よくぞおいで下さった
ミス·ヘクマティアル
You're quite young.
ずいぶんお若い方なのですな
It's a pleasure to meet you, Major Pollack.
はじめまして　ポルック少佐
Sorry about my subordinates. They're a bit on edge.
部下がご迷惑をピリピリしておりましてね
We've taken the eight anti-aircraft
missiles from your containers.
コンテナの対空ミサイル8基　しかと受領しました
Then Major, if you could just sign--
では少佐　さっそくこちらにサインを
Now, now. There's no need to rush.
いやいや
そんなに焦らずとも
Please take a seat.
どうぞお掛けになって
When did things fall into such a state of affairs?
何時からですか　こんな状況になったのは
Just eight hours ago.
つい八時間前です
Wasn't Lieutenant Colonel
Grant supervising this delivery?
納入責任者はグラント少佐のはずでは
You know this happens a lot.
よくいるんです
いざ戦いとなるとブルってしまうキャリア
In this line of work, some
bolt once the fighting starts.
So, simply pretend he was never here to begin with.
まあ　初めからいなかったということで
Yikes! I wish I never asked.
うわあ　聞かなきゃよかった
This is bad! Extremely bad.
マズイ　非常にマズイ
This battlefield is already ablaze.
この戦場は完全に燃え上がっている
And this commanding officer
is starving for more weapons.
この指揮官も更なる武器が欲しくてほしくてきりがない状態
There's no satisfying him.
That desire will engulf him.
飲み込まれる
Here's my signature.
Also, I hate to add to the order, but...
サインです
それとですな
追加注文と言っては何ですが
See? Here it comes!
ほら　来た
What's this?
あれぇ
I knew it!
やっぱそうだ
Koko, long time no see!
ココちゃん　お久しい
Mildo! And Lou?!
ミルド
あとルーも
Huh? Koko, where's Valmet?
あれ　ココちゃん　バルメは
Valmet's working elsewhere.
バルメは別動中
For you and Lou to be here...
ミルドとルーがうろついてるってことは
おや　奇遇ですな
Goodness! What a coincidence, Koko Hekmatyar.
ココ·ヘクマティアル
President Curry of England's CCAT!
イングランドCCAT社　カリー社長
"Coincidence," my butt.
何が奇遇だ
FN FNC：全长1000mm 重量4.445kg 口径5.56mm*45 装弹数20/30 发射形式S/F/3 制造国：比利时
What do you want?
何の用だ
Who's this? A new recruit?
何こいつ
新入り
ウケる　超ウケる
Too funny! What a joke!
What did you order from Mr. Curry?
カリー氏からは何を
スティンガー
FIM-92"Stinger"：全长1520mm 重量10.1kg（本体） 直径：70mm 装弹数1 制造国：美国
"Stingers."
New missiles with used launchers.
中古の発射器
新品の弾体
We gathered them up in Eastern Europe.
東ヨーロッパ中から集めました
Isn't it great?
いいですね　また戦闘ヘリが蚊のように落ちるさまを見物できるわけですね
We'll get to see attack copters
drop like mosquitoes again.
He's going to scramble
out of here the second he can.
そこでとんずらするつもりのクセに
Cheap, numerous, and powerful!
安く　多く
強い
That's what satisfies our customers the most.
これが現場で最も喜ばれる商品です
Thanks for the explanation.
ご高説どうも
The contract has been fulfilled.
契約は完了です
--Now then, we shall be taking our--
--Hold it! I need to order something!
では我々はこのへんで
待って下さい　追加の話だ
What is it?
何
A radar unit.
レーダーユニット
My radar site was destroyed in an air raid.
空爆で破壊されたレーダーサイト
I need a battlefield radar
unit to work as a substitute.
その代替となる野戦レーダーが必要です
おお　そこまでの大物となると私の手に余る
Something that big is beyond me.
私だってそんなの持ってな
I don't have anything like--
You have one, don't you?
持ってますよね
You're the offspring of navy giant, Floyd Hekmatyar.
海運の巨人
フロイド·ヘクマティアル　その実子
A chunk of HCLI's naval weapons
department for Europe and Africa
HCLIヨーロッパ·アフリカ兵器運搬部門
is run in person by none other than Koko Hekmatyar!
その現場担当の一翼を担っている　ココ·ヘクマティアル
There's no way you couldn't
procure a meager radar unit.
そんな貴女がレーダー程度を調達できないわけがないのです
This old fart intends to use us as scapegoats!
このジーサン
私達をスケープゴートにする気か
I can't! I can't do what I can't do!
無理
無理なもんは無理
--I can't! I can't do it!
--What's going on?
無理～無理だよ～
お　なんだなんだ
I won't let you leave!
逃がさん
Men!
総員
H&K MP5A4：全长680mm 重量2.54kg 口径9mm*19
装弹数15/30/40 连射速度800rpm 发射形式S/F 制造国：德国
黙って見てりゃ　てメーらふざけんな　やろー
We heard you out. Now cut the crap, you bastard!
H&K USP Compact：全长173mm 重量725g 口径 9mm*19
装弹数13+1 制造国：德国
Lutz, control yourself.
ルツ　抑えろ
Let's not do this. We aren't in a Chinese movie.
止めましょうよ　チャイニーズムービーじゃないんですから
Major Pollack, you look tepid,
but you're feisty, aren't you?
ポルック少佐
あなた　ぬるい顔して結構やり手よね
Your control over info is too perfect.
キマリ過ぎの情報統制
You're having the mountain infantry kill
峠越えて逃げる民間人　ジャーナリスト
any civilians and journalists who flee over the pass.
みんな山岳兵に殺害させてるでしょ
That's how desperate you are to
keep this battle for the pipeline a secret.
そこまでして隠したいパイプライン争奪戦
Do you plan on keeping it for yourself?
利権を自分で握る気
Jeez, you make me sound terrible...
いや　そんな人聞きの悪い
But you know what they say.
でも　よく言うでしょ
"Soldiers earn their money by killing people."
「兵隊は人を殺して金をもらう仕事」
Going by that definition, my men are quite adept.
そういう意味では我が部隊はかなりやり手です
You work hard to strengthen
those soldiers with weapons
そんな軍隊を武器で固めて
できるだけ長生きさせようと頑張るあなたたちは
so they survive for as long as
possible, making you, "righteous."
正義だ
I absolutely must have your goods.
私はあなたの商品がどうしても欲しい
Please see justice done.
正義を遂行して下さいよ
Well then, I'm counting on you for that radar unit.
では　レーダーの件お願いします
I have to run out for a bit.
私はちょっと失礼しますよ
あ　お金のことはご心配なく
Oh, don't worry about the money.
Looks like the storm has passed, huh? Well?
嵐が通り過ぎちゃったみたいだね　ね
いやはや　新指揮官
Goodness gracious.
Their new commanding officer is a dangerous man.
厄介な男ですな
別に
Not really. Why don't you hurry on home?
早くお家に帰れば
Toodles!
じゃね
So? What're we doing, Koko?
で
どうすんだ　ココ
There's nothing to be done.
どうするも何も
バルメとトージョも捜さないとね
We need to look for Valmet and Tojo.
According to my investigation,
this army is just about out of funds.
私の調べでは
ここの軍資金はもうかつかつ
He sounded tough, but notice how
he meant he'd pay once he wins?
威勢のいいこと言ってたけど
つまりこの紛争に勝ったらお金を払うってことでしょ
There is no way I, Koko Hekmatyar,
would agree to accept credit!
この私が
ココ·ヘクマティアルが
後金で契約する分けないじゃん
Hey, Tojo. Shouldn't we have
waited for Koko at that pass?
ね　トージョ
やっぱりさっきの峠でココを待ってるべきだったんじゃないですか
I know, but it's not our fault they raided the area.
んなこと言ったって　踏み込んじゃったんだから　仕方ないでしょ
They're still going at it
even though the sun is setting.
日が暮れるってのにまだやってるぜ
Talk about freaky!
超コェエー
What's with this battlefield?
なんなんですかこの戦場は
まるであり地獄です
They're acting like ant lions!
おー　まさにそんな感じだね
Oh, you nailed it!
Let's run by the pass in the morning, Chief.
朝にまた峠に行って見よう　姉御
--We'll keep our guard up.
--Right.
気をつけてさ
そうですね
At least we got to charge our cells.
携帯の充電もできてることだし
I haven't slept under the stars...
屋根なしで寝るなんて
ホント　久しぶりです
...in ages, sheesh.
About contacting HCLI headquarters...
HCLI本社との連絡ですが
Your cells will work again once you cross the pass.
峠を越えれば携帯電話が復活します
Your precious iridium cell doesn't work here, does it?
虎の子のイリジウム携帯も通じないでしょう
铱卫星：铱卫星是美国Motorola公司提出的一种利用低轨道卫星群实现全球卫星移动通信的方案。
This is one of the only places
out of its range in all of Europe.
ヨーロッパの中で数か所しかない圏外なのです　ここは
なんだ　持ってるの知ってたんですね
What, you knew I had one?
You're right. We're out of range.
ホントだ　圏外
I'll have two of my elites accompany you.
精鋭2名同行させましょう
You can make it through the hazardous pass
safely as long as they're with you.
彼らがいれば危険な峠も安全に移動できます
They're my "collars," huh?
首輪　ね
Well, take care.
それではお気をつけて
Please don't pretend to
accept my offer and then flee.
引き受けた振りして逃げないでくださいね
Tch! Who do you think
you are, dumbass arms dealer?
チッ　武器商が何様っつの
しゅっ　出発後十分で早くも悪態
H-He's cursing me out ten minutes after departure?
You're just adding oil to the fire...
and burning human lives!
火に油注いでんだけだぜ
燃えてるのは人の命だ
Radom VIS35：全长205mm 重量1025g 口径.22LR 9mm*19
.45ACP 装弹量10+1 8+1 7+1 制造国：波兰
いい大学出た秀才さんが　んなことも分からねえのか
Can't you brainiacs from good colleges see that?
I'm just a merchant
私はただの商人だし
and I've never attended a place
that matches the image of a "school,"
大学どころか　学校と名を付く所には通ったことがないからなあ
let alone attended college...
But regardless,
だがしかし
I've spent far more time with my "wares"
私と商品との付き合いは
君が精鋭となるまで銃を握った時間よりはるかに長い
than you have with that
gun before becoming an elite.
I find watching my merchandise
go to soldiers in name only
君のような名ばかりの部隊の元に私の商品が届くさまは
as depressing as looking at a calf.
まるで子牛を見ているように憂ウツだよ
It pisses me off. Keep quiet
when you aren't giving directions.
気が立っている
道案内以外は黙っていろ
FN Hi-Power MK3：全长200mm 重量986g 口径9mm*19 装弹数13/20 制造国：比利时
What was that, you brat?!
んんだと　ガキ
This is Orin Pass.
ここがオリン峠だ
It's so foggy!
凄い霧
Jonah, Jonah! We might
be able to get through now.
ヨナヨナ
そろそろ通じるかも
Could you give it a try? Call Tojo.
試しにかけてみてくれる　トージョって
It's ringing.
呼び出してる
It's ringing? Sweet!
やった
Mi-24V 雌鹿E型 当年的新科技研发型，1976年量产至1980年代才被西方世界得知，装备更多9M114
Shturm（AT-6反战车导弹）。四个派龙架可以装八枚，这也是产量最大版本，超过1500架。
Mi-24V　ハインドE
Mi-24V Hind E's!
They're the Russian army's Hinds!
ロシア軍のハインドだ
Whoa!
Everyone, hide! Get away from the car!
みんな　隠れろ
車から離れるんだ
攻撃してる
They're firing...?
Is the mountain infantry nearby?
近くに山岳兵がいるのか
スティンガー
A Stinger...
It missed!
外してるし
何だ貴様ら
Who're you?
The weapons dealer that met with Major Pollack.
ポルック少佐と会った武器商だ
Is a different unit shooting the Stingers?
スティンガーを撃ってるのと別の部隊か
I can't tell that to a civilian!
民間人に答えられん
They're all dead.
Get your unit away from the Hinds.
彼らは全滅だ
貴方の隊をハインドから遠ざけろ
あの機体は人狩り専用
That device is meant for hunting people.
Look at the sensor pod. That's a thermal sensor.
センサーポッドを見ろ
あれはサーモだ
It's a normal low-light-level TV "Radoga-F"
通常のLLLTV「ラドガ·F」が東欧サードパーティー製に換装されてる
LLLTV："low light level television"的简写，中文名为微光电视设备
that has been modified by
an Eastern European third party.
If the pilot felt like it, he could see all of us.
パイロットがその気になったら
私達は丸見えだ
That was a close one!
危なかったですね
This woman... Wasn't she smiling the whole time?
この女
終始笑ってなかったのか
She's nuts!
いかれてる
Get the heck out of here, Lucky Girl!
さっさとここから失せろ　ラッキーガール
I was planning to!
言われなくても
Why don't you just sell him the weapons?
何で素直に売ろうとしないの　武器
Jonah, my intuition says that
this battle will be over in two days.
ヨナ
私の勘では
この戦闘はあと二日で終わる
It's not going to end by one side defeating the other.
どちらが勝って決着ということではない
Russia is unable to focus on all of their battlefronts
いくつもの戦線に集中できないロシアと
and the major has ambition but lacks money.
野望はあっても金がない少佐
I suspect that this gray-area
war is going to turn chronic.
灰色の戦いが慢性化すると私は踏んだ
That means no one will obtain the money-gushing
spring, or possession of the pipeline.
それは金の湧く泉　パイプラインの所有権もどっちつかずという意味だ
There are dealers who would love
this mess and flood them with weapons.
むしろ泥沼を好んで武器をきりなく流し込む商人もいるが
Actually, that's the norm.
というか　そっちが主流だが
But because of the way I do things,
私の経営方針「やり方」からは
この戦場　商売相手として魅力がなくなった
I've lost interest in doing
business on this battlefield.
So we're trusting your "intuition"?
ココの「勘」を信じるのか
Right. Everyone has put their faith
in my intuition as an arms dealer.
そう
H&K G36K：615（860）mm 重量3.0kg 口径5.56mm*45 装弹数10/30/100 连射速度750发/分 发射方式S/F S/2/F 制造国：德国
皆を乗せた　武器商人の勘だよ
Not satisfied?
ご不満かな
USSR AKS74U "Krinkov"：全长730（490）mm 重量3.2kg 口径5.45mm*39
装弹30 连射速800发/分 发射形式S/F 制造国：苏联
Why you--!
貴様ら
Colt Government (US M1911)：全长216mm 重量1077g 口径.45ACP .38Super 装弹数7+1 9+1 制造国：美国
Wh-What were you thinking, Mildo?!
何をやっておるか　ミルド
Dang, I'm pissed! I don't care
if they were "elite" or whatever,
えー　もう逆鱗
精鋭だかなんだか　知んないですけど　ずっとべちゃくちゃ煩いの
they were friggin' annoying!
The major may have given us those
"collars"to serve as ID to cross the pass!
少佐が我々にも首輪をつけたのは
峠を越えるための通行証の意味だったのかもしれんのだ
My plan's in shambles!
I can't believe you! Imbecile!
計画がぱあだ
信じられん　馬鹿もん　戦闘狂
Battle-hungry freak!
Give me the map.
地図を出せ
He's quick to recover. That's the president!
回復早
さすが社長
What are you talking about?
何を喋っている
I'm confirming where we're
supposed to pick up the goods with HQ.
本社と品物の受け取り場所を確認している
Koko, what should we do with those two?
ココ　その二人は
Be quiet and don't kill them.
殺さず静かに
Tie them up!
縛っちゃれ
Oh, and gag him. He's annoying!
そっちの奴　口もね
うるさいから
Jeez, Valmet! I was so worried.
もうバルメ
心配したよ
Y-You know I was as well, Koko!
も　もちろん　私をです　ココ
Wha-hoo! This feels heavenly!
これは素晴らしい気分です
Okay! Everyone's here, right?
よっしゃあ　皆揃ったね
Let's move it.
移動だよ
Ah! My nose's bleeding!
あ　鼻血
Tch!
Whoa, there. If it isn't Lou!
おいおい　んだ
ルーかよ
Hey, it's CCAT's guys! It's okay to come in!
おーい　CCAT社の連中だ
入ってOKだ
No, it's not okay.
いや　OKというわけでは
Well, well! President, fancy running into you here.
あらあら　社長
妙なとこで再会ですね
What a coincidence!
奇遇ですね
And here I thought you'd be
arriving in England about now.
もうイギリスに到着しているころと思ってたんですが
Long time no see!
久しぶりい
Mildo?
ミルド
I'm interested in you.
私　あんたに興味があるんだ
Your lifestyle never ceases to intrigue me.
興味が尽きないの
バルメの生き方
And that offensive power of yours!
そしてあんたが手にしたその攻撃力
It makes me want to beat you up.
叩きのましたくなっちゃうんだ
I don't really care about you.
私は　別に　何も
President!
社長ーー
Shut up! It's your fault we're
in this mess! Watch yourself!
煩い
お前のせいで　こうなったのだ
自重しろ
I can't watch myself!
自重できません
Did you kill the major's "collars"?
少佐の首輪を殺しましたか
No, but we did tie them up and leave them behind.
いいえ　縛って放置して来ましたけど
That stupid woman killed ours!
こちらのはあの馬鹿女が斬ってしまった
Trackers may come here looking for us.
ここもいずれ追っ手が来るかもしれない
They definitely will!
絶対来るよ
Why don't we have those two scout the area?
あの二人に外で斥候をさせてはどうか
Valmet, I'm really sorry! Please!
バルメ　本当にごめん
お願い
Piece of cake.
余裕です
I can't turn one of her
requests down. I'll play with you.
あの子の頼みなら仕方ありませんね
付き合ってあげましよう
Koko's changed, hasn't she?
ココちゃん　変わったよね
Ages ago, she was amazing.
ひと昔前はすごかった
But she's way better now.
今のほうが断然いいよ
She was and still is awesome.
ココは昔も今も最高です
Here I go!
行くぞ
Nice, nice! You rock!
いいじゃん　いいじゃん
凄い
Why can't I even graze you?
なんで　掠りもしない
You're at a huge disadvantage
in knife fights with that eye.
あんた　ナイフ戦で大きなハンデなんだよ　その目
But since I never win,
I challenged you at night this time!
それでも毎回勝てないから
今度は夜に挑んだのに
I have good night vision! What gives, Valmet?!
私　夜目が効くんだよ
どうなってんの　バルメーー
Your movements seem somewhat
stiffer than last time, Mildo.
なんだか前回より　動きが鈍くなった気がします　ミルド
I understand wanting to carry all of those knives,
そうやってナイフたくさんって気持は分かりますけど
but is it wise to let them
hamper your sides and back?
腰や脇の邪魔になるようでは　拙いのでは
Even Jonah, our new recruit,
said that you're "covered in knives."
うちの新入りヨナ君も
あなたのこと「ナイフだらけ」て
His name is Jonah, huh?
ヨナって名前なのか　あれ
Were you planning to lure me
to the knife you threw and go,
大方こうやって放ったナイフの近くに私を誘導して
"Here's my chance! I'll snatch
this back up and use it!"
チャンス　引っこ抜いて再利用
"You let your guard down,
Valmet!" or something like that?
「油断してなバルメ」みたいな戦法
あ
What's with the yelp?
何が「あ」ですか
Once a weapon has left your hands,
consider it gone for good! It's common sense.
一度手から離れた得物は二度と使えないと思え　常識です
Crap! She's entered lecture mode.
しまった　説教モードだ
Koko Hekmatyar and her
subordinates create a group of ten.
十人組がココ·ヘクマティアルとその部下で
The group of three is Curry and his men from CCAT.
三人組がカリーのCCAT社だ
I want you to prioritize the group of ten.
私が重視するのは十人の方
But at the same time,
do not forget that while you're out,
だが同時に君たちがいないことで
Orin Pass and the freeway that crosses
the border will be left wide open.
オリン峠及び越境国道のひとつがフリーなのを忘れてはいけない
Roger, Major.
了解　少佐
But the group of three killed two of our comrades!
でも　三人の方は同僚を二人殺してます
I'm fully aware of that!
言われなくても分かってる
I think you should reconsider, Mildo.
考え直してみては　と思いますけど　ミルド
Back in that clock factory, you
said that you were interested in me,
さきほど　時計工場の中で
私に興味があるっておっしゃてましたが
but that isn't terribly wise.
お勧めできません
Why not?! You're so cool!
なんで
あんた　かっこいいじゃない
You were a military elite,
but got betrayed and lost everything.
軍のエリートだったのに
裏切りですべて失って
Then you trained yourself some more
and got back on your feet! Too cool!
そのあとさらに自分を鍛えこんで立ち直った
クールだよ
You're overestimating me.
買いかぶりですし
And while you mean nothing to me,
ミルドは私にはどうでもいい人ですが
I'd rather you didn't have to go
through the same experience I did.
それでも私と似たような経験はして欲しくないです
I've never had anything to begin with!
私なんか　はじめっから何もないもんね
People like us who fight with
weapons might be empty voids.
私らみたいに武器持って戦ってる人間って
空虚なのかもしんないね
We're empty! But is it from the first
time we kill someone with a weapon?
空っぽなの
はじめて武器で他人をやった時から
From the time we first hold a weapon?
武器を握った時から
"We did it to protect our family or our country!"
家族を守るだの国を守るだの
Those are just excuses made up after the fact.
そんなのはあと付けの理由なんだよ
Even I can tell that much.
そんくらい私でも分かるよ
I get the feeling my void will be filled
戦いの技術がバルメに追い付いたら
once my fighting level is on par with yours!
なんか空っぽが埋まるような気がするんだよね
That's stupid.
馬鹿な
Valmet, I'll let you off for today!
バルメ
今日はこれくらいにしといてあげる
But I'll kick your butt next time!
次は必ず　ぷっ倒す
You've picked up the presence of
trackers, haven't you? Their distance?
追っ手の気配を感じたんですね
距離は
Five hundred meters!
五百メートル
President!
社長ーー
This is the only thing that girl excels at.
あの子　こういう感覚だけは鋭いんですけど
Prepare for battle!
戦闘準備
We'll go first and create an escape route.
我々が先に出て突破口を開きます
Depending on the opponent,
we may be able to subdue them.
相手にもよりますが制圧できるかもしれない
I'll begrudgingly let you owe me one.
仕方なく「ひとつ貸し」ですよ
My, your bravery lives up to
my expectations, Hekmatyar!
ほお　さすがの勇ましさですな　ヘクマティアル
Later! Bye, Mildo!
そてでは　バイ　ミルド
There aren't a whole lot of them,
but they have us surrounded.
たいした人数じゃねえが　囲まれてる
Everyone in my unit,
我が隊　総員
lower your weapons!
武装解除
What?!
なに
Remove your cylinders. Fold your stocks!
弾倉を抜き
ストックをたため
MP5K：全长325mm 重量2000g 口径9mm*19 装弹数15/30/40
连射速度900rpm 发射形式S/F 制造国：德国
Listen, mountain infantry!
聞け　山岳兵
We are the group of ten!
我らは十人
The group of three is inside!
三人は中にいるぞ
That vixen!
あの女狐
Crap! Shit!
くっそ　くっそ
FN P90：全长500mm 重量3.0kg 口径5.7mm*28 装弹数50
连发速度900发/分 发射形式S/F 制造国：比利时
Don't expect this to work every time.
こんな手が毎回通用すると思うなよ
Since we're away from our post,
俺たちがいないから　その間だけオリン峠からの国境はスルーだ
you can slip through Orin Pass to the border.
Head north, Lucky Girl.
北に向かえ　ラッキーガール
Everyone, dash!
We're escaping from this killing field!
みんな　ダッシュ
キリングフィールドからエスケープだぜいえ
What's gotten into you, Jonah?
どうかしたかね　ヨナ君
Nothing.
別に　でも
But it feels strange.
変な感じなんだ
It's the first time I didn't shoot
a single bullet on the battleground.
戦場で一発も撃たなかったのははじめてだ
All right! I'll let you shoot
a whole bunch next time, Jonah!
よし
じゃあ　次は山ほど撃たせてやるぞ　ヨナ
It's about time you realized, Jonah,
そろそろ　分かれって　ヨナ坊
that kind of remark will fly right over her head.
お嬢には思わせぶりな台詞は通用しね
She's a weapons dealer!
彼女は武器商人なんだぜ
It's unfortunate that both sides escaped.
両方ともとは参ったね
They're pretty good, too.
なかなかやるな彼らも
Blame you? I don't blame you.
責め
責めなどしないよ
I can understand your decision and shall support it.
君たちの選択を理解できるし　支持もしよう
Taking responsibility is part
of my job, so don't you take it.
責任は私の仕事だ
取らないでくれ
Right. Return to your post.
そうだ　持場に戻ってくれたまえ
It's also a fact that the air raids
stopped the second this arrived.
こいつが来たとたん　空爆がぴたりと止んだのも事実
Their wares can put on a fierce
show or become scrap metal.
激烈な示威にも鉄屑にもんらる奴らの商品か
The weapons dealer Koko Hekmatyar...
武器商人　ココ·ヘクマティアル
She's one crazy lady.
まったく　ふざけた女だ
--It ended in a day?
--Ma'am?
一日で終わったか
はい
Oh, no, it's nothing.
いえ　なんでも
--May you have a pleasant trip.
--Thanks.
良い旅を
ありがとう
W-We made it!
つつ　着いた
President, I'm exhausted!
社長ーー　疲れた
Oh, so they survived.
おお　生きとったか
Hikari yokotaeru wadatsumi
光横たえる海神
光怪陆离的海底龙神
Soukon no ma ni yurameku ayamachi
創痕の間に揺らめく過ち
累累创痕之间摇曳着缕缕罪孽
Fujou shite iki wo tsugi
浮上して息を継ぎ
浮出水面 吸清吐浊
Tokasare majiru dake no zouai wo te ni shita
溶かされ混じるだけの憎愛を手にした
爱与恨 如漆似胶 如影随形
Mujun haramu
矛盾孕む
矛盾诞世
Kono sekai goto
この世界ごと 覆い尽くしてる策動の音に傾く夢
冥冥的梦中 世界渐渐倾浸于欺言诡语之中
Ooitsukushiteru sakudou no ne ni katamuku yume
Ashi wa mou nai
脚は　もう無い
足膝 已没入虚无
Suiheki wo tsuranuku kodou
水壁を貫く鼓動
透过水壁 传来阵阵鼓动..
恶魔岛字幕组(bbs.emland.net)
诸神字幕组(kamigami.org)
本字幕由   恶魔岛字幕组   &   诸神字幕组   联合制作
(bbs.emland.net)    (kamigami.org)
翻译 TL旧民        日听 yaya
注释 TL旧民        日听 奶昔
后期 aoi           压制 娜夏
仅供交流学习之用 禁止用于商业用途
诸神字幕组
恶魔岛字幕组
时轴 两仪
Her name is Koko.
She is loco.
I said, "Oh no!"
Her name is Koko.
She is loco.
I said, "Oh no!"